美国家庭影院 出品
联合制作: 梦工厂 与 PLAYTON公司
领衔主演:科克・阿塞沃多 埃昂・贝利 迈克尔・库德利兹
里克・格梅兹 斯科特・格里米斯 弗兰克・休伊斯
达米安・路易斯 朗・利文斯通 詹姆斯・马迪奥
尼尔・麦克唐纳 雷内・L・莫雷诺 大卫・休默
道格拉斯・斯佩恩 理察・斯贝特 唐尼・沃尔伯格
角色的分派: 利伯曼/巴顿
视觉效果总监:安格斯・ 比克尔顿
特殊效果监督员: 乔斯・威廉姆斯
服装设计师: 安娜・谢帕德
编辑:比利・福克斯
音乐:迈克尔・凯曼
制作设计 : 安东尼・布拉特
摄影指导:乔尔・ J・ 兰塞姆
监督指导: 艾力克・简得森
制作人: 玛丽・理查兹
监督制片人: 埃里克・ 柏克
联合执行制片人: 史蒂芬・安布洛斯 加里・高依兹曼 托尼・ 托
执行制片人:汤姆・汉克斯 斯蒂文・斯皮尔伯格
兄弟连作者: 史蒂芬・安布洛斯
写作:格雷厄姆・约斯特 与 布鲁斯・C・麦肯纳
导演: 大 卫・纳 特
兄 弟 连
The Toccoa men, that's the ones that was there at the very beginning.
那群老鸟从大战开始就在那儿了
They are very close and...
他们的感情很好
...they accept people coming in like myself...
他们也欢迎象我这种菜鸟
...as a replacement.
来做补充兵
But you also had to prove yourself.
但你得证明自己的能力
Most of them were, we know were qualified parachutists.
我们知道他们大部分都是合格的伞兵
They had to be.
一定得是
A lot of them were awfully green...
他们许多人都很嫩
...and we knew that.
这我们也知道
We just... We hoped we could keep them alive...
我们只希望他们能保住性命
...or they could keep alive, a lot of them didn't.
虽然许多人还是阵亡了
But, well, all right, they eventually blend right in.
但是 他们终于还是适应了
I think maybe they were trying to...
我想他们是想
...impress the older guys people like me or Shifty.
在象我或西福弟这样的老鸟前求表现
I don't know why but I got right there to where...
我不知道是为什么 但我...
...I didn't wanna be friendly with replacements coming in because...
就是不想给这些补充兵好脸色 因为...
...God, I didn't like seeing them get killed.
我不想看到他们被杀
I just, it just tore me up.
这让我痛彻心扉
We were in awe of them.
因为我们很敬畏他们
They were wearing infantry badges, you know the uniform.
他们穿着制服 绣着伞兵臂章
They had a star on their jump wings.
徽翼中还绣上星星
They...
他们...
They were like heroes to us, you know?
对我们而言他们是英雄
That's how we looked at them.
我们就是这样看待他们的
And they were good. Furthermore, they were good.
他们都很厉害 而且人不错
We had good officers, for the most part...
我们的军官大都不错
...but we had excellent NCOs.
但士官们更是了得
They looked... They looked after you.
他们一路照顾着我们
第四集
新 兵 支 援
( 1944年9月13日)
( 英国 爱德布恩 )
Lieutenant, nice and easy. We've still got a shot.
好了 中尉 慢慢来 你还有一支
Tough break, you're having a tough night.
你今天晚上手风不顺
People have tough nights.
谁都会这样
I'm sorry, George.
我很抱歉 乔治
It's all right.
没有关系
Nice shot, sir.
射的好 长官
Thank you, Bull.
谢谢你 大牛
Thank you, Lieutenant.
谢谢你 中尉
Finish me up.
看看你能不能赢我
Here we go.
开始吧
Double seven.
射七的两倍
You're embarrassing the Lieutenant here.
你让中尉下不了台了
Have a drink.
来 喝一杯
Don't mind if I do, Sarge.
请原谅我让你难堪 班长
Better start winning money soon.
我们最好快点开始赢钱
I think your buddies miss you.
你的兄弟开始在想你了
Yeah, they do look kind of sad, don't they?
对 他们看来有些沮丧吧?
They're just serious fighting men, that's all.
他们只是认真的战士而已
Well, I think I'm gonna go introduce myself.
我想过去做个自我介绍
Careful what you say now.
小心你的措辞
Don't take much to set my guys off.
我的弟兄是很容易被激怒的
Yeah, and you got some wild-eyed killers right there.
对 你的弟兄还是冷血杀手呢
It's a good thing we weren't gambling.
我们没有打赌是对的
Boy, we would've gotten killed.
不然我们会被痛宰
Wanna bet? What?
要打赌吗?
What?
什么?
You wanna bet?
你要打赌吗?
No, I'm not much of a gambling man.
我不太会赌博
Hey, come on.
来吧 赌包烟
First one to hit the bull's-eye?
看谁先射中靶心?
Yeah, one shot. One shot.
好 只射一次
Yeah? Make it two
好啊 我再加一包烟
Two packs.
两包烟
All right, two packs, here we go. One shot, very good.
好 两包烟 我们开始吧 只射一支
Hey, fellows.
各位
What do you hear? What do you say?
有什么消息吗? 你们在聊些什么?
Actually, that's Babe's seat, Private Heffron's.
那是二等兵赫夫朗的位子
Is that right?
是吗?
I don't care if it's fucking Eisenhower's.
就算是艾森豪威尔的位子我也不管
Who are you?
你是谁?
Private Miller, James Miller.
二等兵詹姆士米勒
I'm in Sergeant Randleman's squad.
我是蓝道曼中士手下的
Us too, I'm Les Hashey.
我们也是 我叫莱斯赫胥
Tony...
东尼
Garcia, I know who you are.
贾西亚 我知道你是谁
Old Gonorrhea don't miss nothing.
我是不会认错人的
Lieutenant, are you gonna shoot lefty all night?
中尉 你要一直用左手射吗?
Hey, come on.
别这样
Just curious as he's right-handed.
我只是好奇嘛 他又不是左撇子
George. What would I do without George Luz?
我少了乔治鲁兹要怎么办?
Bu...Bo...
中!
Goodness gracious.
老天爷
Two packs, gentlemen.
两包烟 各位
I know you got them, pay up.
我就知道你行
So, Heffron tell you about Doris yet?
赫夫朗告诉你们桃莉丝的事没有?
No.
没有
No?
没有?
Well, then I'm gonna educate you.
那..让我来告诉你们
We're about to get on a plane...
我们正要上飞机
...for that first frog town we never jumped into.
跳伞到一个不知名的小镇去
All of a sudden, Heffron stops dead in his tracks.
突然间赫夫朗站定不动
Bing and a bang and a boom everybody banging into each other.
害得大家都撞成一团
Heffron's just staring up at the plane's nose, because...
赫夫朗盯着机首猛看 因为...
...on it is painted this beautiful pinup.
上面..有张很漂亮的美女照
And written underneath: "Darling Doris".
底下还写着"亲爱的桃莉丝"
Doris just happens to be the name of the skirt who just...
桃莉丝是那姑娘的名字
...that day, sent Babe one of them letters.
她那天寄给贝比那封叫什么的信来着?
You know the...
那个...
What do you call them letters that the broads send?
马子寄来的信要怎么说?
Dear John letter.
分手信..
That's it, a "Dear Babe" letter.
就是这个! 贝比的分手信
Well, anyway, lucky for Babe, Patton overruns our drop zone.
不管怎样 算贝比运气好 巴顿已占领了我们的空投区
Mission cancelled. In other words...
任务就取消了 换句话说...
...Babe don't have to risk getting inside old Doris again.
贝比不用再冒险进入桃莉丝的身体里了
Hey, Bull, your squad listens up real good.
大牛 你的弟兄真是好听众啊
Yeah, they're being polite like whenever Bull opens his mouth.
无论大牛说什么 他们都表现得毕恭毕敬
What are you saying?
强尼 你在说什么?
Bull's boys are humoring him?
大牛的弟兄只是在迁就他?
Like whenever he gives out some of his folksy wisdom from back down on the farm.
对 就象是当他传授所谓的家乡智语录时
Probably think he's a fucking hayseed.
他们可能以为他真是个乡巴佬
They're right.
对不对?
What are you laughing at?
你们笑什么?
You new boys, you pay attention to Sergeant Randleman.
菜鸟们! 要听蓝道曼班长的话
Got that?
知道吗?
That's the smartest man in the company.
他是连里最聪明的人
Where'd you get that?
你从哪儿拿到这个的?
It's a Presidential Distinguished Unit Citation.
这是总统杰出单位褒扬状
For...
为了...
For what the Regiment did in Normandy.
为了本团在诺曼底的表现
That's right, for what the Regiment did.
没错! 为了"本团"的表现
You weren't there.
你没有参与
Hey, hey, ease up, Cobb?
火气别那么大 卡伯
It's a unit citation.
那是团队的表扬奖状
Shit, Cobb.
去你妈的 卡伯
You didn't fight in Normandy neither.
你也没参与诺曼底战役
I got hit in the plane before I got a chance to jump.
我跳伞前在机舱内就受伤了
Hey, you all, listen up.
你们全部都听好了
I got us an announcement to make.
我有个消息要宣布
This here is Carwood Lipton.
这位是卡伍德・李普
He's already married, Smokey.
他已经结婚了 史摩基
This here is Carwood Lipton:
这位是卡伍德・李普
The new Easy Company 1st Sergeant.
Ｅ连的新任上士
As befitting his position...
为了配合他的职位
...he says he has to make an announcement.
他说有事要向大家宣布
Well, hate to break the mood here, boys, but...
很不愿扫大家的兴 可是...
...we're moving out again.
我们又要出动了
As you can see...
正如大家所见
...this is called Operation Market-Garden.
这叫"市场花园行动"
In terms of airborne divisions involved...
以空降师的参与程度来说
...this one's even bigger than Normandy.
这次规模比诺曼底还要大
We're dropping deep into occupied Holland.
我们要深入荷兰德军占领区
The Allied objective is to take this road here...
盟军的目标是 占领...
...between Eindhoven and Arnhem...
恩荷芬与安恒之间的道路
...so the two British armored divisions can move up it...
让两个英国装甲师能够...
...toward Arnhem.
朝安恒移动
Our job is gonna be to liberate Eindhoven.
我们的任务 就是解放恩荷芬
Stay there, wait for the tanks.
留在那儿 等坦克来
The entire European advance has been put on hold to allocate...
整个欧洲先头部队已经停下来
...resources for this operation.
为这次行动分配资源
It's Montgomery's personal plan...
这是蒙哥马利个人的计划
...and we'll be under British command. - Yippee.
我们将归英军指挥
The good news is, if this works...
好消息是 如果这次作战成功...
...these tanks will be over the Rhine and into Germany.
这些坦克就可以渡过莱茵河进入德国
It could end the war and get us home by Christmas.
这将结束战争 那样圣诞节前我们就能回家了
It'll be a daytime jump.
跳伞将在白天进行
Intelligence doesn't expect much opposition.
情报显示应该不会有太激烈的抵抗
They think the Krauts in Holland are mostly kids and old men.
他们认为在荷兰的德军大部分都是老人和小孩
And we should take them by surprise.
而且我们会出其不意
In any case, say goodbye to England.
总之 跟英国说再见吧
I don't think they're gonna call this one off.
我想他们不会取消这次作战
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?
Look at Cobb, man.
你看看卡伯
Watch and learn, kids.
边看边学吧 孩子们
You wanna live?
你们想活命吗?
Jump ready to fight.
跳伞前做好战斗准备
They let you out of the hospital like that, boy?
他们就让你这个样子出院?
They didn't let me out, I busted out.
他们没让我出院 我逃出来的
I didn't wanna get reassigned to some other unit.
我不想被派到其他单位去
Can you make the jump?
你还能跳伞吗?
Sure I can, Lip, I just can't sit.
当然可以 李普! 我只是不能坐下
Welcome back, Popeye.
欢迎归队
Thanks, Bull.
谢谢你 大牛
Popeye went AWOL just in time to jump.
他开小差出院刚好赶上跳伞
What's he doing here?
他在这儿做什么?
Who, Sobel?
索伯吗?
Well, he's the newly appointed regimental S4.
你是新派来的团部S4
Supply officer?
补给官?
Yeah, you got it.
你说对了
He picked me up in Aldbourne...
他在艾德波恩遇到我
...trying to find you guys.
问你们的下落
He know you went AWOL?
他知道你是开小差从医院逃出来的吗?
He knows.
他知道
He just said I was lucky...
他只是说我运气好
...I could sit out this jump if I wanted.
如果我不愿意跳的话大可退出
I said I didn't want to.
我说我要跳
So he says, "Hop in."
他就说 "上车"
"Hop in"?
"上车"?
Yeah, I know, I couldn't believe it either.
我也不敢相信
Maybe he's gonna court-martial me later?
说不定迟点他就会送我上军事法庭
Let's get you some gear.
我们去拿你的装备吧
Hey, Mal.
嘿 马拉其
Over there.
看那里
Son of a bitch.
混蛋
Malarkey.
马拉其
Sergeant Malarkey.
马拉其中士
Sir?
长官?
You thought you'd get away with it?
你以为你逃的掉?
What do you mean, sir?
什么意思 长官?
Sergeant, that motorcycle is United States Army property.
中士 那辆摩托车是美国陆军的财产
That may not mean anything to you...
它对你可能毫无意义
...but it means something to me.
但对我就不同了
Where'd you find it?
你在哪里找到它的?
That's him all right.
一点也没有变
Who is he, Sarge?
他是谁啊 中士?
He was our first CO.
他是我们第一任连长
What happened?
发生什么事?
He got promoted.
他晋升了
Just tap my leg, Sergeant.
拍我的腿就是了 中士
Lieutenant, you'll be in the doorway.
中尉! 你要站在门口的
Yeah, I know, but...
我知道 可是
Look, Sergeant, you'll be the man behind me.
听着 中士! 你排在我后面跳的
When the green light comes on if you could just tap me, all right?
当绿灯亮起时 你就拍我的腿
The green light will be next to you, sir.
绿灯就在你旁边 长官
Just do it, that's an order.
照做就是了! 这是命令!
Come here, come here.
过来
Sling it around, and when you land...
肩枪姿势着地时
...your knee'll hit the butt.
膝盖会撞到枪托
The business end'll break your jaw.
会打烂下巴的
Lose your reserve, you don't need it. We'll jump low.
扔了副伞 用不到那个 跳伞高度很低
Take your belly band and wrap it around you. Fine.
把腹带绕着穿好 很好
( 1944年9月17日 荷兰 )
I'm sorry, Sarge.
抱歉班长
Don't be sorry.
没关系
Grab your rifle, let's go.
带着步枪 我们走
Where'd you get that from, Hoobler?
哪儿弄来的 胡伯勒?
I think I love Holland.
我想我爱荷兰
Where'd you get these?
这些从哪儿弄来的?
That farmhouse over there.
在那边的谷仓里
Just sitting out in the open.
就放在那里
I don't know, maybe they were expecting us.
我不知道! 也许他们早等着我们来了
Boys?
弟兄们
Made it.
我们成功降落了
I wonder if they hit anything.
我怀疑他们打到什么没有
Goodbye air support.
再见了 空中支援
There's some kind of holdup ahead.
前方停下来了
We're going in through this field here.
我们要穿过这块田
Move out, let's go! Let's go, move it, move it!
出发了! 快! 快点!
You won't be able to shoot as straight with that thing on.
上了刺刀打不准的
Okay, hold your fire.
不要开枪
( 荷兰 恩荷芬 )
Hey, kid.
嘿 小子!
Bull!
大牛!
Bull, you seen Captain Winters?
大牛! 你有看到温特斯上尉吗?
No, why?
没有! 什么事?
Keep your squad moving.
叫你的班继续前进
Where are all the Germans?
德国人在哪儿?
They could be anywhere.
他们随时都会出现
Keep moving!
继续前进!
Pardon me.
对不起
Come on, lady.
别这样 小姐
Dick, clock's ticking.
迪克! 没时间了!
Yeah.
我知道
Thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you, thank you.
谢谢你...
Very kind.
你真好
What's up, Welshy?
怎么了 威尔旭?
Snipers.
有狙击手
We've gotta get to these bridges.
我们得到达这些桥梁
Sergeant Talbert.
泰伯特中士...
Let's move, we've got work to do.
我们走 我们还有活要干
What did they do?
她们做了什么?
They slept with the Germans.
跟德国人睡觉
They are lucky.
她们算运气好
The men who collaborated are being shot.
跟德军合作的男人都被枪毙
Mr. Van Kooijk here is with the Dutch resistance.
梵固克先生是荷兰反抗军成员
We've been waiting and hoping for this day...
我们一直期待着这一天
...for almost five years.
等了快五年了
Says he can help us secure the bridges here.
他说可以帮我们守这座桥
Together we can push the remaining Germans...
我们可以一起将剩下的德军
...out of Eindhoven.
逐出恩荷芬
And that's just the beginning.
而且这只是个开始
Any idea where they might be?
知道德军的行踪吗?
Well, we're still working on that right now.
我们还在努力中
Pius and his friends here are getting information as we speak.
我们说话的时候 彼德和他的同伴们 已经在搜集情报
His contacts, a couple of towns down...
他在几个村落外的联络人
...saw the British 2nd and Guards Armored pass half an hour ago.
说他们看到英军第二装甲师和(爱尔兰)禁卫装甲师在半小时前通过
They're kids.
他们只是小孩子
These are reliable reports.
这些都是可靠的消息
Anything we can do to help you, we will do.
任何能帮忙的事我们都愿意做
Anything.
任何事
Right on time.
真准时
Captain.
上尉
I'll be happy to show you the quickest route to the bridges.
我很乐意带你去看前往桥梁的捷径
I'd be happy to have your help.
我很高兴有你的帮忙
Get scouts to the edge of town...
派警戒兵驻守镇的外围
...in case we're here for the night.
说不定我们要在此过夜
Hey, Van Klinken.
嘿 凡克・林肯
Webster.
韦伯斯特
Sleeping outside is for suckers, guys.
在外面睡觉的是笨蛋
Better be good, I was almost asleep.
最好是好事 我都快睡着了
Heraus, Hande hoch.
不准动! 手举起来!
Mach schnell.
( 荷兰语 )
Niederlander. Niederlander.
我是荷兰人 荷兰人!
Sprechen Sie English?
会说英文吗?
Ja.
会
A little bit.
一点点
What were you doing down there?
你在下面做什么?
It's an air-raid shelter.
这是个防空洞
My family has been in there...
我们从第一架飞机飞过后
...ever since the first plane flew over.
就一直躲在那里面
We're Americans.
我们是美国人
Paratroopers.
美国伞兵
The Germans...
德国人...
...are gone?
他们走了?
Think so.
我想是吧
You see any, you let us know.
如果你有看到就通知我们
Are you here to stay?
你们会留下来吗?
As long as we have to.
该留多久就留多久
Yeah, they don't tell us very much.
对 上级说的不多
Or feed us much.
也没给我们多少食物
Please wait here.
请等一下...
You see that?
看到没有?
I say screw Paris.
我说去他妈的巴黎
Hey, don't talk about screwing, all right?
别说脏话 好吗?
They all speak English.
他们都说英文
They all love us.
也都爱我们
What a fantastic country.
真是个很棒的国家
Hey, take a look.
嘿! 你们瞧!
Here, take.
这里! 拿着!
Danke.
谢谢
Are these olives?
这都是我们的吗?
Thanks, danke.
谢谢
Ja, komme wieder, es ist gut.
你可以出来了
Zigaretten?
要香烟吗?
Ja.
好
He never tasted chocolate.
他从来没有尝过巧克力
It's pretty good, isn't it?
很好吃 对不对?
Oh, man, you know what?
我的天 你知道吗?
I hate this!
我讨厌鸡蛋!
Here, Sarge, you can have this one.
班长 你可以吃这个
Vincent van Gogh was born in Nuenen.
梵高就是在努安南出生的
Yeah?
是吗?
So what?
那又怎样?
Sure teach a lot of useful stuff at Harvard.
在哈佛学的东西还真有用
Mellett.
梅略特
Hey, get a load of General Patton.
他好象跟巴顿将军学了不少
What the hell's he doing?
他在搞什么鬼?
Makes quite a target, don't he?
很好的活靶 不是吗?
Lieutenant!
中尉!
Sniper!
狙击手!
Charge!
班长!
Clear the track!
离开马路
Move it!
躲到坦克后面去!
Come on, come on!
快点!
Medic up front, medic up front!
我这里要医护兵!
What should we do?
我们该怎么办?
Keep down, stay still.
姿势放低 不要乱动
Keep moving!
继续前进!
Get up! Keep moving!
起来! 继续前进!
Keep moving!
继续前进!
He's shooting stationary targets!
他会射击不动的目标!
Move!
快走!
The farmhouse, deploy right.
到农舍的右侧
Take the right side.
你攻右边
Right.
好的!
Go.
去!
Go on.
前进!
Kraut!
德军!
Shit.
可恶!
God damn it, move!
可恶 快移动!
Go, come out, come out!
走 出来!
Away, away, away!
离开..离开...
What's he saying?
他在说什么?
He said:
他说...
"Away, away,"...
"离开 离开"
...which either means that the Germans have gone...
意思是德军已经走了
...or he wants us to go.
或是要我们离开
I don't know.
我不确定
Go, go!
走!
Ramirez!
蓝姆雷兹
Beat it!
准备!
All right, fellows, set them up.
来弟兄们 快点架好
Tiger.
虎式坦克
Shit!
糟了!
Heffron, on me.
赫夫朗! 跟我来!
Stay low.
蹲下
You got a can opener, Babe?
你有开罐器(火箭筒)吗? 贝比?
Afraid I don't, Sarge.
我恐怕没有 班长
We've got a Kraut tank...
前面有德军坦克
...100 yards on the left.
位置在一百码外建筑的左侧
I don't see him.
我看不到
Put some shells through that building...
你开几炮打穿那幢建筑
...you gonna see him real good.
就会很清楚的看到它
I can't.
我不能那么做
My orders are no unnecessary destruction of property.
我收到的命令是非必要情况不得损毁财产
I'm telling you, he's right there.
我告诉你它就在那里
And I believe you.
我相信你
And if I can't see the bugger...
但如果我看不到目标
...I can't bloody well shoot him, can I?
我就打不准 对吧?
Are you staying or going?
你要待着还是离开?
He's gonna see you real soon.
他很快就会看见你了
What the hell's he doing?
他在干什么?
Forward, roll tank!
前进!快点!
Fall back!
撤退!
Pull back, pull back!
快撤退!
Take cover!
找掩护!
There's a ditch on the other side.
另一边有战壕
Follow me through.
跟我过去
Van Klinken!
凡克・林肯!
Bull!
大牛!
Go!
快走!
Rifle grenade!
枪榴弹!
Schmitz, MG-42.
史密斯! MG-42机枪!
Ten o'clock, nail them.
10点钟方向 干掉他们!
Fire!
开火!
You had to leave him.
你得丢下他
He's still alive!
他还活着!
Who's hurt?
谁受伤了?
Van Klinken.
凡克・林肯
Other side of that hedge.
在树篱的另一边
Oh, shit!
可恶!
Okay, ready.
准备好了
Fall back, fall back, fall back!
撤退!
Pull back, Alley, pull back!
撤退 艾利 撤退!
Go!
走!
Pull back!
撤退!
Take over.
接手
Yeah, where?
好 去哪儿?
We have to get him to the rear.
我们得送他到后面去
What are we gonna do, Lieutenant?
我们该怎么办 中尉?
I'm not sure.
我不确定
Sir, they're about to unflank us.
长官 他们快击溃我们的侧翼了
We gotta get out of here!
我们得赶快离开这里!
We have infantry everywhere.
四周都是德国步兵
Repeat, Arnhem has cut the road.
重复! 安恒道路遭到阻断
We are covered in infantry.
我们四周都是敌人的步兵
We are pulling back.
我们要撤退了
Luz, fall back!
鲁兹 撤退!
撤退!
Hash, where's Randleman?
赫胥! 蓝道曼在哪里?
I don't know, Sergeant.
我不知道 中士
Get out of here!
快离开这里!
Miller!
米勒!
Come on.
走吧!
Hashey, let's go!
赫胥 我们走!
Get down!
放低!
Medic!
医护兵!
Go, get a medic, keep moving!
找医护兵来!继续前进!
- Hey, doc. - Lieutenant.
- 嘿 医生 - 排长
It's gone right through.
子弹穿过去了 巴克
Side to side, both cheeks.
大腿两侧被打穿了
Malarkey, get them out of here, go!
马拉其! 带弟兄们离开这里!
What?
什么?
Leave me here for the Germans.
就...把我留给德军
You nuts? We'll carry you.
你疯了吗? 我们会背你的
Are you kidding me?
你开玩笑吗?
I weigh more than both of you two guys combined.
我比你们两个加起来还重
Come on.
走吧!
What the hell are you doing?
你在搞什么鬼?
Help us!
来帮我们!
Get back to the tank!
退回坦克那边!
Keep moving, keep low!
继续走! 姿势放低!
Let's go, let's go.
快来 我们走
Over you go.
快上车
One bullet, four holes.
一发子弹四个洞
Yeah, it's almost a miracle.
这也算是个奇迹
Lip, I don't think we know where Bull is?
李普! 我想没人知道大牛的下落吧?
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
继续走!
Keep moving, keep moving!
继续前进!
Move them out, let's go!
继续走!
Hurry up, let's go!
我们快走!
How bad?
有多糟?
I don't know yet.
我还不知道
Nix!
尼克!
I'm all right, I'm all right.
我没事
- Am I all right? - Yeah
- 我没事吗? - 对
Yeah, you feel all right?
你还好吗?
Yeah, quit looking at me like that.
还好 别这样盯着我看
Captain, we got four dead.
上尉! 我们死了四个弟兄
Eleven injured.
伤了十一个
Okay, let's move them out.
好! 我们带他们离开!
And, sir, Randleman's missing, too.
长官! 蓝道曼也失踪了
Randleman?
蓝道曼?
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
Okay, let's go.
好吧 我们走
Where's the Bull?
大牛在哪儿?
Don't know.
不知道
I never fired a shot, the whole time.
我从头到尾没开过一枪
Find anything out?
发现什么了吗?
About what?
有关什么?
Anything.
什么都好
What we're doing next.
我们下一步要怎么办?
No.
不知道
I did hear one thing.
不过我倒听说了一件事
Lieutenant Brewer's gonna make it.
布鲁尔中尉会活下来
What?
什么?
Lieutenant Brewer's gonna make it.
布鲁尔中尉撑过来了
There's no way.
不会吧 怎么可能
He's headed back to England.
已经回英国了
They'll probably send him home.
他们可能会送他回家
How is that possible?
这怎么可能?
He did turn his head at the last second.
蓝道曼中士叫住他时
When Sergeant Randleman called out to him.
他的确在最后一刻回过头来
No.
不
Just pull...
拔...
Fuck.
可恶
Just pull it out.
拔出来就对了
Go, go!
快走!
Hoob.
胡伯
Any news of the Bull yet?
有大牛的消息没有?
If there ain't no body...
没看到尸体
...then there ain't nobody fucking dead.
就表示人没有死
Understand me?
懂吗?
I'm gonna look for him.
我要去找他
Not by yourself you're not.
你不准自己一个人去
I'll go with you, let me get some ammo.
我跟你去 让我去拿些弹药
That's okay.
不用了
I'll go.
我也去
Me, too.
我也是
All right.
很好
Go get him.
把他找回来
All right, what the hell...
好吧! 不管那么多了
I ain't going back up there.
我才不要再回去
Webster, us or them?
韦伯斯特! 是我军还是敌军?
Not us.
不是我们的人
Stupid. Stupid.
真是蠢 蠢货
Stupid.
蠢货
Go.
走
They're bombing Eindhoven.
他们在轰炸恩荷芬
Yeah.
是啊
Come on, Nix.
来吧 尼克
We'll dig in for the night.
我们晚上有事做了
Won't be waving so many orange flags at us tomorrow.
明天不会有那么多橘旗子向我们挥舞了
Where the fuck you been?
你死到哪里去了?
Glad to see you boys.
很高兴能见到你们
Not as glad as us.
我们比你更高兴
Bet you thought we'd given up on you there, boss?
你一定以为我们抛弃你了 对吧 老大?
Shut up, Cobb.
闭嘴 卡伯!
What?
怎么了?
I think we should go back now.
我想我们现在该回去了
Hey, Johnny, look.
强尼 你看
Bull!
大牛!
Hey, Johnny.
嘿 强尼
Get a little lost?
有点迷路了吧?
Something like that.
大概是这样
It's good to see you.
真高兴看到你
me too.
我也是
I don't know whether to slap you, kiss you, or salute you.
我不知道是该打你亲你 还是向你敬礼
I told these scallywags you was okay.
我告诉这些老土你不会有事的
And they didn't listen?
但他们还是不听?
These salty bastards...
这些大老粗们
...wanted to do a suicide run...
就是要出这个自杀任务
...to drag your ass back.
去找你回来
Is that right?
真的吗?
Yeah, I told them, "Don't bother."
对 我就说别麻烦了
I never did like this company none.
我从来就没这么喜欢过这个连
Hoobler.
胡伯勒
So, they found you.
他们找到你了
Wait, what did you say?
等等 你刚说什么?
Johnny, don't irrigate me!
强尼 别惹我!
"They found you"?
"他们找到你了? "
I don't know who's more stupid, you or the hick.
我不知道是谁比较蠢 你还是乡巴佬?
All right, mount up!
好了 着装! 动作快点!
Hup hup, let's move out!
出发了!
Grab your gear, let's go!
取装备 我们走!
2nd Platoon, grab your gear!
第二排 取装备!
Let's go!
出发了!
1st Platoon!
第一排!
Let's start falling in now.
我们归队吧
Cobb, move it.
卡伯 动作快点
Dukeman, round them up.
杜克曼 叫他们集合
1st Platoon.
第一排!
Grab your gear, let's go!
拿上装备 出发了!
Van Kooijk says the Germans are concentrating...
梵固克说德军装甲部队
...their armor up near Veghel.
在维格尔附近集结
We may be heading into some more tanks.
我们可能会遇上更多坦克
Well, as long as it's only old men and kids.
只要都是老人和小孩就好
Yeah.
没错
I don't like retreating.
我不喜欢撤退
First time for everything.
凡事总有第一次
How are the other divisions faring up north?
别的师在北方进展如何?
I think we're gonna have to find another way into Germany.
我想我们得找别的路进入德国
"市场花园"是一次失败的高风险作战
盟军计划在1944年圣诞节前结束战争并未成功
Ｅ连所属的506团中阵亡180人 受伤560人
整个101空降师阵亡750人 2100人受伤
英国第一空降师在安恒损失近八千名弟兄